Indiana University President's Office records, 1962-1968 C304
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1962-1968
  - Association (Box 13)
    - American Heart Association, Appraisal of report on President's Commission on Heart Disease, Cancer, and Stroke, 1964-1965 (Box 14)
    - American Heart Association, Jan.-May 1965 (Box 14)
    - American Management Association, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - American Medical Association, 1964-1967; (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - American Medical Association, cont.'d (Box 15)
      - 1963-1964, (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - Association of American Colleges, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 15)
    - Association of American Law Schools, 1967 (Box 15)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 15)
    - Association of American Universities, 1962-1968; (3 folders) (Box 15)
      - Conference-AAU-ACU-NCCUC, London, Ontario, September 1964; (3 folders) (Box 15)
    - Association of American University Press, 1963-1964 (Box 15)
    - Association of American Universities, 1964-1965 (Box 15)
    - Association of College Unions (Box 15)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 15)
      - Campus Conference, 1962-1963 (Box 15)
    - Association of Commonwealth Universities, 1966-1968 (Box 15)
    - Association for Counselor Education and Supervision, 1965 (Box 15)
    - Association of Governing Boards of State Universities and Allied Institutions (Box 16)
      - 1966-1968 (Box 16)
      - Reports, 1966-1968 (Box 16)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 16)
      - Compact for Education Panel, October 13, 1965; 1964-1966 (Box 16)
      - 1962-1965, (3 folders) (Box 16)
    - Association of Graduate Schools, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - Graduate Cultural Association, 1964 (Box 16)
    - Association for Higher Education, 1963-1964 (Box 16)
    - Highway 37 Association, 1964-1965 (Box 16)
    - Association Internationales des Etudiants en Sciences Economiques et Commerciales, (International Assocation of Economics and Business Students), 1966-1968 (Box 16)
    - International Association of Universities (Box 16)
      - 1966-1968 (Box 16)
      - Publications, 1965-1966 (Box 16)
      - Meeting in Tokyo, Japan, Summer of 1965; 1964-1965 (Box 16)
      - Tokyo trip, Aug. 25-Sep. 13, 1965; 1964-1965 (Box 16)
      - Report, 1962-1964; (3 folders) (Box 16)
    - International Association of Universities Presidents, 1968 (Box 17)
    - International Association of University Professors (and lectures), 1964-1965 (Box 17)
    - Midwest Association of student financial aid administrators, ca. 1967 (Box 17)
    - Midwest Universities Research Association (Box 17)
      - 1963-1968, (5 folders) (Box 17)
      - Proposal for a high intensity accelerator, 1963; (2 folders) (Box 17)
      - Jan.-Mar. 1964 (Box 17)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 17)
    - Campus Ministry Association, 1966 (Box 17)
    - Mississippi Valley Historical Association, (now Organization of American Historians), 1965; (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Modern Language Association of America, 1966-1968 (Box 17)
    - National Aeronautic Association, 1965-1966; (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 17)
    - National Association of College and University Attorneys, 1963-1969 (Box 17)
    - National Association of Schools of Music, Self-Survey Report, 1967 (Box 18)
      Conditions Governing Access
      (Restricted)
    - National Association of State Universities (Box 18)
      - Transactions and proceedings, 1963 (Box 18)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 18)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant College, 1966-1968; (3 folders) (Box 18)
      - 1966-1968, (3 folders) (Box 18)
      - Joint Office of Institutional Research, Survey Project, 1963-1965 (Box 18)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 1962-1968; (2 folders) (Box 18)
      - Athletic Medicine, Apr.-Aug. 1968 (Box 18)
    - National Education Association (NEA) (Box 18)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 18)
      - Erroneous use of data from Bureau of Census, 1962-1964 (Box 18)
      - Association for Higher Education, 1964-1965 (Box 18)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 18)
      - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 18)
      - American Association of School Administrators, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 18)
      - Association for Higher Education, 1966-1968 (Box 19)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 19)
      - Association for Higher Education, 1963-1966; (2 folders) (Box 19)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 19)
      - Association for Higher Education, 1962-1963 (Box 19)
      - Department of Higher Education, National Conference on Higher Education, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 19)
      - Educational Policies Commission, 1964-1965; (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - National Rifle Association, 1964-1965; 1968; (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - National Security Industrial Association, 1965-1966 (Box 19)
    - National University Extension Association, 1964-1966; (3 folders) (Box 19)
    - North Central Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 19)
    - North Central Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, Annual Meeting, 1963-1964; (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - Association of Schools and Colleges of Optometry, Record of the Annual Meeting, 1962; 1965; (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - Southern Assn. of Colleges and Schools, Mar.-Apr. 1964 (Box 19)
    - Association of State Colleges and Universities, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - State Universities Association, 1962-1966; (3 folders) (Box 19)
    - University Research Association, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - University Research Association, Inc. (URAI), 1965 (Box 19)
    - Western History Association, 1963-1964; (3 folders) (Box 19)
  - Astronomy, 1963-1968 (Box 19)
  - Astronomy, Department of, 1962-1966; (2 folders) (Box 20)
  - At, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 20)
  - Athenaeum Turners, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 20)
  - Athletics (Box 20)
    - 1962 (Box 20)
    - Basketball (Box 20)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 20)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 20)
        - U-Z, 1962-1963 (Box 20)
        - R-T, 1961-1963 (Box 20)
        - M-Q, 1962 (Box 20)
        - G-L, 1962-1963 (Box 20)
        - A-F, 1962-1963 (Box 20)
      - General, 1962 (Box 20)
      - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 20)
      - Tickets-Complimentary (Box 20)
        - 27 Nov. 1962 (Box 20)
        - 1963 (Box 20)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 20)
        - U-Z, 1963 (Box 20)
        - R-T, 1963-1964 (Box 20)
        - M-Q, 1963-1964 (Box 20)
        - G-L, 1963-1964 (Box 20)
        - A-F, 1963-1964 (Box 20)
        - General, 1963-1964 (Box 20)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 20)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 20)
        - U-Z, 1964 (Box 20)
        - R-T, 1964-1965 (Box 20)
        - M-Q, 1964-1965 (Box 20)
        - G-L, 1964-1965 (Box 20)
        - A-F, 1964-1965 (Box 20)
        - General, 1963-1964 (Box 20)
        - Tickets-Complimentary, 1965 (Box 20)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 20)
      - 1966 (Box 20)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 20)
        - U-Z, 1965 (Box 20)
        - R-T, 1965-1966 (Box 20)
        - M-Q, 1965 (Box 20)
        - G-L, 1965-1966 (Box 20)
        - A-F, 1965-1966 (Box 20)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 20)
      - Tickets, 1965-1966 (Box 20)
      - Tickets, 1967 (Box 20)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 20)
        - U-Z, 1967 (Box 20)
        - R-T, 1966-1967 (Box 20)
        - M-Q, 1966-1967 (Box 20)
        - G-L, 1966-1967 (Box 20)
        - A-F, 1966-1967 (Box 20)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 20)
        - U-Z, 1967 (Box 20)
        - R-T, 1967 (Box 20)
        - M-Q, 1967 (Box 20)
        - G-L, 1967-1968 (Box 20)
        - A-F, 1967 (Box 20)
      - Television Contract, 1961-1967 (Box 20)
    - Athletics Committee, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 20)
    - Football, 1964-1968; (5 folders) (Box 20)
      - Mr. Burton's File, 1967-1968 (Box 20)
      - Correspondence (Box 20)
        - U-Z, 1966 (Box 20)
        - R-T, 1965-1966 (Box 20)
        - M-P, 1966 (Box 20)
        - G-L, 1966 (Box 21)
        - A-F, 1965-1966 (Box 21)
        - U-Z, 1967 (Box 21)
        - R-T, 1967 (Box 21)
        - M-P, 1967 (Box 21)
        - G-L, 1967 (Box 21)
        - A-F, 1967 (Box 21)
        - U-Z, 1968 (Box 21)
        - R-T, 1968 (Box 21)
        - M-P, 1968 (Box 21)
        - G-L, 1968 (Box 21)
        - A-F, 1968 (Box 21)
        - U-Z, 1965 (Box 21)
        - R-T, 1965 (Box 21)
        - M-Q, 1965 (Box 21)
        - G-L, 1965 (Box 21)
        - A-F, 1965 (Box 21)
      - Games and Luncheons, 1965 (Box 21)
      - Game Invitations, 1967 (Box 21)
      - Kentucky Game, 1967 (Box 21)
      - Pre-game ceremonies, 1965 (Box 21)
      - Purdue Game (Box 21)
        - 1965 (Box 21)
        - 1967-1968 (Box 21)
      - Rose Bowl (Box 21)
        - 1967-1968 (Box 21)
        - California, 1967 (Box 21)
        - January 1, 1968, 1967-1968 (Box 21)
        - Official Trip, #1, Nov.-Dec. 1967 (Box 21)
        - Official Trip, # 2, 1967-1968 (Box 21)
        - Official Trip, #3, 1967-1968 (Box 21)
        - Official Trip, Release of Liability, 12 Dec. 1967 (Box 21)
      - Tickets (Box 21)
        - 1966-1968 (Box 21)
        - 1965 (Box 21)
    - Olympic Recognition Dinner, Alumni Hall, 18 Feb. 1965; 1965 (Box 22)
    - Annual Report, 1963-1964 (Box 22)
    - Receipts and Disbursements, July 1, 1963 to June 30, 1964 (Box 22)
    - Receipts and Disbursements, July 1, 1964 to June 30, 1965 (Box 22)
    - General files, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 22)
    - Receipts and Disbursements, 1962-1965; (3 folders) (Box 22)
    - Operating Statements, 1964-1966; (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - Policy on Academic Standards for Students, 1963 (Box 22)
    - Proposal for contracts for Coaches, 1964 (Box 22)
    - Selection of Football Coach, 1964-1965 (Box 22)
    - Student ticket coupons, 1964 (Box 22)
    - Televising Athletic Events Contracts, 1963-1965 (Box 22)
  - Atlantic Council of the United States, Inc., 1962-1967; (3 folders) (Box 22)
  - Au, general, 1962-1998; (5 folders) (Box 22)
  - Audiovisual Center, Annual Report, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 22)
  - Auditorium, 1963-1966; (3 folders) (Box 22)
  - Auditorium (Box 22)
    - (includes Annual Report), 1963-1964 (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 22)
    - Operating Statements, 1966-1967 (Box 22)
    - Organ, 1963-1968 (Box 22)
    - Schedule, 1966-1968 (Box 22)
    - Twenty-Fifth Anniversary, 1963-1966; (2 folders) (Box 22)
  - Audubon-Acceptance of Audubon Reproduction, May 1966 (Box 22)
  - AUSA-Indiana Chapter, 1965-1966 (Box 22)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises, 1964-1966; (2 folders) (Box 22)
  - Auxiliary Services-Consensus Regarding Auxiliary Services at Selected Universities, 1966 (Box 22)
  - B, general (Box 22)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 22)
    - 1962-1966, (4 folders) (Box 23)
  - Bacteriology Botany, 1964-1965 (Box 23)
  - Bad, general, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Baghdad, University of, (Mosul, Iraq), 1964-1965 (Box 23)
  - Bai, general, 1966-1968 (Box 23)
  - Bain, Dean Wilfred C., 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 23)
  - Bak, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 23)
  - Bal, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 23)
  - Balfour, L.G., 1966-1968 (Box 23)
  - Ball Residence Operating Statement, July 1, 1964 to June 30, 1965; 26 Jan. 1965 (Box 23)
  - Ball State University, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Ball State Teachers College, 1962-1965; (3 folders) (Box 23)
  - Bank Reconcilement, 1962-1963 (Box 23)
  - Ban, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 23)
  - Bar, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 23)
  - Barker, Joseph B., 1966-1967 (Box 23)
  - Barr, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 23)
  - Bart, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 23)
  - Bartley, E. Ross, 1962-1963 (Box 23)
  - Bas, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 23)
  - Bat, general, 1966-1968 (Box 23)
  - Bau, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 23)
  - Bayh, Birch E., Jr., 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 23)
  - Be, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 23)
  - Bec, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 23)
  - Beck Chapel, 1963-1968 (Box 23)
  - Bee, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 23)
  - Bel, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 23)
  - Ben, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 24)
  - Benn, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 24)
  - Benton, Thomas Hart-murals, 1966-1968 (Box 24)
  - Ber, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 24)
  - Bern, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 24)
  - Berry College, Mount Berry, Georgia, 1964 (Box 24)
  - Bes, general, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 24)
  - Brian Bex Report, Archives copies, 1966-1968 (Box 24)
  - Bi, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 24)
  - Bin, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 24)
  - Biochemistry, 1964-1965 (Box 24)
  - Division of Biological Sciences (Box 24)
    - 1962-1967, (6 folders) (Box 24)
    - Natural Area Preserve, 1963-1965 (Box 24)
  - Biro, Sari, 1962-1963 (Box 24)
  - Bl, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 24)
  - Glenn A. Black Laboratory (Box 24)
    - 1965-1967 (Box 24)
    - Annual Report, 1966-1967; 1967 (Box 24)
  - Black Student Demands and related papers, 1966-1968 (Box 24)
  - Blak, general, 1962-1963 (Box 24)
  - Blo, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 24)
  - Bloomington, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 24)
    - Boy Builders, 1962-1964; (3 folders) (Box 25)
    - Chamber of Commerce (Box 25)
      - Priorities Committee, ca. 1962 (Box 25)
      - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 25)
      - Housing Survey, 1967 (Box 25)
    - Country Club, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 25)
    - Daily Herald-Telephone, 1965-1966 (Box 25)
    - Hospital (Box 25)
      - Fact Sheet, 1963 (Box 25)
      - 1962 (Box 25)
      - Building Fund, 1967-1968 (Box 25)
      - Building Fund-Background material for campaign, 1967 (Box 25)
    - Houses and Rentals, 1964-1966 (Box 25)
    - Kiwanis Club, 1962-1967; (5 folders) (Box 25)
    - Mayor's Redevelopment Advisory Committee, 1962-1965 (Box 25)
    - Metropolitan Schools and University Schools, 1963-1966 (Box 25)
    - Metropolitan Schools (Box 25)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 25)
      - 1962 (Box 25)
    - National Bank (Box 25)
      - 1968 (Box 25)
      - 1965 (Box 25)
    - Rotary Club, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 25)
    - Transit Lines, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 25)
    - United Fund, 1964; (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - Water Rates, 1965-1966 (Box 25)
  - Blue Cross-Blue Shield Hospitalization Insurance, 1932-1968; (5 folders) (Box 25)
  - Bo, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 25)
  - Board for Fundamental Education, 14 Nov. 1967 (Box 25)
  - Board of Regents, "Super-board" proposed for Indiana State-sponsored Schools, 1966-1967 (Box 25)
  - Board of Trustees (Box 25)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 25)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 26)
    - Camp Brosius Meeting, June 27-30, 1965; 22 Jun. 1965 (Box 26)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 26)
    - Camp Brosius Meeting, 1964 (Box 26)
    - 1962-1964 (Box 26)
    - Information Manual, 1962 (Box 26)
    - 1962-1964, (3 folders) (Box 26)
    - Letters to the Members, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 26)
    - Minutes, President Stahr's Copy, 1962; 1966-1967; (3 folders) (Box 26)
    - Notices, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 26)
    - Agenda, Dr. Stahr's file, 1966-1968 (Box 26)
    - Agenda Items, 1965-1966 (Box 26)
    - Policy on registration of Student Organizations, 1966-1967; (2 folders) (Box 26)
    - President's General Report, 1962-1964 (Box 26)
  - Bobilya, Ruth, 13 Nov. 1964 (Box 26)
  - Boh, general, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 26)
  - Bon, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 26)
  - Bonds-Miscellaneous, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 26)
  - Bookstore, I.U. (Box 26)
    - 1962-1968, (4 folders) (Box 26)
    - Annual Report, 1962-1967; (3 folders) (Box 26)
    - Balance Sheets, 1964-1965; 1965 (Box 26)
    - Operating Statements, 1964-1967; (3 folders) (Box 26)
      - Branch 1 Operating Statements, 1964-1965 (Box 26)
      - Medical Center Operating Statements, 1964-1965 (Box 26)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 26)
      - Foster Quad, Operating Statements, 1963-1964 (Box 26)
      - Medical Center Operating Statements, 1963-1964 (Box 26)
      - Smithwood Hall Operating Statements, 1963-1964 (Box 27)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 27)
  - Booth, David B., 1966-1968 (Box 27)
  - Booz, Allen & Hamilton, Inc., 1962-1968 (Box 27)
  - Bor, general, 1962-1968 (Box 27)
  - Borden Company Foundation, Inc., 1965 (Box 27)
  - Bos, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 27)
  - Bow, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 27)
  - Boy Scouts of America, 1963-1968; (2 folders) (Box 27)
  - Boys' Club, 1966 (Box 27)
  - Br, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 27)
  - Brademas, John, 1965-1967; (2 folders) (Box 27)
  - Braden, Samuel (Box 27)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 27)
    - Calendar, 1962-1963 (Box 27)
  - Bradford Wood Recreation Center (Box 27)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 27)
    - Operating Statements, 1963-1964 (Box 27)
    - 1963-1966, (3 folders) (Box 27)
    - Annual Report, 1966 (Box 27)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 27)
  - Bradfute Building, 1962-1966 (Box 27)
  - Branigin, Roger D., 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 27)
  - Bray, William G., 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 27)
  - Brazil, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 27)
  - University of Brazil-"Sister University" Relationship Proposal, 1964-1965 (Box 27)
  - Bre, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 27)
  - Bren, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 27)
  - Bri, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 27)
  - Brin, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 27)
  - Bro, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 27)
  - Broo, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 27)
  - Brookings Institution (Box 28)
    - 1965-1968, (2 folders) (Box 28)
    - Annual Report, 1963-1965; (2 folders) (Box 28)
  - Brow, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 28)
  - Brown County Playhouse, 1963-1965 (Box 28)
  - Brown University Alumni Dinner honoring President-elect Heffner, 1966 (Box 28)
  - Bru, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 28)
  - William Lowe Bryan Administration Building-Notices, Form Letters (Box 28)
    - 1964-1968 (Box 28)
    - 1 Mar. 1966 (Box 28)
  - Bu, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 28)
  - Budget (Box 28)
    - 1963-1968, (3 folders) (Box 28)
    - Biennial, 1962-1968; (2 folders) (Box 28)
    - Other Schools, Feb.-Mar. 1966 (Box 28)
    - Summaries and Comparative Data, 1965-1966 (Box 28)
    - Supporting Papers, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 28)
    - Committee Meeting (Box 28)
      - February 29 and March 1, 1968 (Box 28)
      - October 7-8, 1966 (Box 28)
    - 1965-1968, (4 folders) (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964-1965 (Box 28)
    - Other Schools, 1963-1964 (Box 28)
    - Biennial, 1964-1968 (Box 28)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 28)
    - Apr.-May 1964 (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 28)
    - Biennial, 1962-1965 (Box 28)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 28)
    - Biennial, 1962-1963 (Box 28)
    - Presentation to Governor, Four State Schools Capital Appropriations Request for, 1965-1967; 1964-1965 (Box 28)
    - Supplies and Expense Summary, 1965-1966 (Box 28)
  - Bue, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 28)
  - Buildings, 1963-1967 (Box 28)
  - Buildings and Grounds Service Acct., 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 28)
  - Bur, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 28)
  - Bureau of Institutional Research (Box 29)
    - 1964-1968, (2 folders) (Box 29)
    - Course profile, 1964-1967 (Box 29)
  - Burk, general, 1962-1967; (3 folders) (Box 29)
  - Burn, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 29)
  - Bursar Annual Report, 1963-1968; (2 folders) (Box 29)
  - Burt, Ista, etc., 1963-1964 (Box 29)
  - Bus, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 29)
  - School of Business, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 29)
    - Dedication, S. of B. Auditorium, November 18, 1966 (Box 29)
      - 1965-1967, (2 folders) (Box 29)
    - Annual Report, 1962-1968; (6 folders) (Box 29)
    - Business Horizons, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 29)
    - Business Placement, 1966-1967 (Box 29)
    - Executive Committee Meetings, 1962-1964; (3 folders) (Box 29)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1962-1968; (3 folders) (Box 29)
    - Indiana Executive Program, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 29)
    - Indiana Executive Program, 1962-1965; (3 folders) (Box 30)
    - Business Placement Office Annual Report, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 30)
  - But, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 30)
  - Butler University, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 30)
  - C, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 30)
  - Cal, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 30)
  - Calendar, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 30)
  - California, 1963-1964 (Box 30)
  - California, University of, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 30)
  - Cam, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 30)
  - Camp Brosius, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 30)
  - Campus, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 30)
  - Campus Bus System, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 31)
  - Campus Conferences (Box 31)
    - Indiana University, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - Education Writers Association, 1965-1966 (Box 31)
    - International Conference on Alcohol and Traffic Safety, 1965-1966 (Box 31)
    - University-Federal Agency Conference (I.U.P.U. & US-CSC), 7 Nov.-10 Nov. 1965 (Box 31)
    - Indiana University (Box 31)
      - 1962-1966, (3 folders) (Box 31)
      - Calendars and Annual Reports, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 31)
  - (Introduction of Dr. Erwin D.) Canham, Clowes Hall, Indianapolis, April 11, 1966 (Box 31)
  - Car, general, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 31)
  - Car, general, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Carm, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 32)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1964-1965 (Box 32)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1962-1968 (Box 32)
  - Carnegie Foundation Commissions-Studies and Reports, 1964-1968 (Box 32)
  - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 32)
  - Carr, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 32)
  - Cars, general, 1962-1968; (3 folders) (Box 32)
  - Cas, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 32)
  - Cash Receipts Vouchers, 1967-1968 (Box 32)
  - College and University Catalog File (Correspondence), 1962 (Box 32)
  - Ce, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 32)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1966-1968 (Box 32)
  - Center for Computer Technology in the Biomedical Sciences, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Proposed Center for Mid-west Development, 1965 (Box 32)
  - Center for Modern Greek Studies (Byzantine), 1963 (Box 32)
  - Center for Neural Sciences, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 32)
  - Center for Research Libraries (formerly Midwest Inter-Library Center), 1965-1967; (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1965-1966; (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Central Microfilm-Annual Report, 1967-1968 (Box 32)
  - Central Stores-Annual Report, 1967-1968 (Box 32)
  - Ch, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 32)
  - Chambers, M.M., 1967-1968; (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Chambers, M.M., 1962-1967; (6 folders) (Box 33)
    - Grapevine, 1962-1966; (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - Indiana Needs No Super-Board for Higher Education, 20 Jun. 1966 (Box 33)
  - Char, general, 1962-1968; (3 folders) (Box 33)
  - Check List, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 33)
  - Checks-Stop Payment, 1962-1968; (2 folders) (Box 33)
  - Chemistry, Department of (Box 33)
    - 1962-1968, (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - Graduate Advisor Annual Report, 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Chi, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 33)
  - Chicago, University of, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 33)
  - Chicago-I.U. Archaeological Project, 1962-1964; (3 folders) (Box 33)
  - Chr, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 33)
  - Christmas, 1963-1968 (Box 33)
  - Christmas Eve on Campus, 1962-1964 (Box 33)
  - Christmas Greetings, By Departments, Conferences, Etc., undated (Box 33)
  - Chueh file, 1962-1967 (Box 33)
  - Chueh, Chih-cheng, Brother of Theresa Yang, 1967 (Box 33)
  - Ci, general, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 33)
  - Ci, general, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 34)
  - Cincinnati Council on World Affairs, 1962-1963 (Box 34)
  - City Planning Associates, Inc., 1964 (Box 34)